{
  "data": [
    {
      "key": 1,
      "question": "You see a man carrying a pitcher of water. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Go to him and offer him help",
      "tags": ["Hands-on", "Decisive", "Friendly"]
    },
    {
      "key": 1,
      "question": "You see a man carrying a pitcher of water. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Follow him to wherever he's going",
      "tags": ["Calm", "Adaptable", "Worshipful"]
    },
    {
      "key": 1,
      "question": "You see a man carrying a pitcher of water. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Observe him and do a vibe check",
      "tags": ["Observant", "Behind", "Focused", "Detailed"]
    },
    {
      "key": 2,
      "question": "You follow the man to a flight of stairs. As you head up, you...",
      "answer": "Light up a candle for better vision, and for better vibes",
      "tags": ["Adaptable", "Detailed", "Creative", "Hands-on"]
    },
    {
      "key": 2,
      "question": "You follow the man to a flight of stairs. As you head up, you...",
      "answer": "Appreciate the beauty of the spiral staircase",
      "tags": ["Creative", "Calm"]
    },
    {
      "key": 2,
      "question": "You follow the man to a flight of stairs. As you head up, you...",
      "answer": "Wish you could take some photos, but alas, the year is ~30 AD",
      "tags": ["Capture", "Behind"]
    },
    {
      "key": 3,
      "question": "You reach a large Upper Room, fully prepared and fully furnished.",
      "answer": "\"Yo, where's Jesus?\"",
      "tags": ["Worshipful", "Focused"]
    },
    {
      "key": 3,
      "question": "You reach a large Upper Room, fully prepared and fully furnished.",
      "answer": "\"Yo, where're my homies Peter and John?\"",
      "tags": ["Friendly", "Creative"]
    },
    {
      "key": 3,
      "question": "You reach a large Upper Room, fully prepared and fully furnished.",
      "answer": "\"Yo, where do I wash my feet?\"",
      "tags": ["Behind", "Hands-on"]
    },
    {
      "key": 4,
      "question": "Choose the one you relate to the most:",
      "answer": "John; I am the disciple whom Jesus loves",
      "tags": ["Worshipful", "Calm", "Focused"]
    },
    {
      "key": 4,
      "question": "Choose the one you relate to the most:",
      "answer": "Peter; I often reply when nobody's asking",
      "tags": ["Decisive", "Detailed", "Creative"]
    },
    {
      "key": 4,
      "question": "Choose the one you relate to the most:",
      "answer": "James; I'm always there when Jesus does amazing things",
      "tags": ["Observant", "Hands-on"]
    },
    {
      "key": 4,
      "question": "Choose the one you relate to the most:",
      "answer": "Thomas; I doubt this quiz is legit",
      "tags": ["Adaptable", "Behind"]
    },
    {
      "key": 5,
      "question": "Everyone has arrived and it's time for the Last Supper.",
      "answer": "Why is everyone sitting on the same side of the table?",
      "tags": ["Observant", "Capture"]
    },
    {
      "key": 5,
      "question": "Everyone has arrived and it's time for the Last Supper.",
      "answer": "*Looks around to see if everyone has their cutlery and utensils*",
      "tags": ["Focused", "Behind", "Detailed"]
    },
    {
      "key": 5,
      "question": "Everyone has arrived and it's time for the Last Supper.",
      "answer": "Start a conversation... perhaps something about greatness?",
      "tags": ["Calm", "Decisive", "Creative"]
    },
    {
      "key": 6,
      "question": "Supper's over and your boy Peter starts spittin claims that he's the greatest. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Do a rugby tackle and take him down",
      "tags": ["Decisive", "Hands-on"]
    },
    {
      "key": 6,
      "question": "Supper's over and your boy Peter starts spittin claims that he's the greatest. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Wait for Jesus to tell him about the roosters",
      "tags": ["Adaptable", "Worshipful", "Calm"]
    },
    {
      "key": 6,
      "question": "Supper's over and your boy Peter starts spittin claims that he's the greatest. What do you do?",
      "answer": "Root for him, but consider how the others might feel",
      "tags": ["Friendly", "Observant"]
    },
    {
      "key": 7,
      "question": "Jesus politely interrupts the conversation and talks about true greatness. At this point, you would be:",
      "answer": "Sitting at His feet to listen to everything He has to say",
      "tags": ["Focused", "Worshipful", "Adaptable"]
    },
    {
      "key": 7,
      "question": "Jesus politely interrupts the conversation and talks about true greatness. At this point, you would be:",
      "answer": "Getting a glass of water in case Jesus gets thirsty",
      "tags": ["Observant", "Hands-on", "Behind"]
    },
    {
      "key": 7,
      "question": "Jesus politely interrupts the conversation and talks about true greatness. At this point, you would be:",
      "answer": "Patting Peter on the back, saying \"There, there.\"",
      "tags": ["Friendly", "Decisive", "Capture"]
    },
    {
      "key": 8,
      "question": "It's time to leave the Upper Room. Before leaving, you...",
      "answer": "Make sure everything is in its original place for the owner of the house",
      "tags": ["Observant", "Hands-on", "Behind"]
    },
    {
      "key": 8,
      "question": "It's time to leave the Upper Room. Before leaving, you...",
      "answer": "Take some selfies with the homies or post an IG reel",
      "tags": ["Capture", "Decisive"]
    },
    {
      "key": 8,
      "question": "It's time to leave the Upper Room. Before leaving, you...",
      "answer": "Thank the owner of the house and ask if you can come again in the future",
      "tags": ["Friendly", "Calm", "Adaptable"]
    }
  ]
}
